Finding Aid for the Tony Barrett Papers PASC.0061
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1. Television and motion picture scripts and production material
  - The Mod Squad (ABC, 1968-1973)
    - DEATH OF A NOBODY by Mann Rubin, 1971 August 27 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - OUTSIDE POSITION by S.S. Schweitzer, 1971 November 17 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - BIG GEORGE by Richard Landau, 1972 January 4 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - NO MORE OAK LEAVES FOR ERNIE HOLLAND by Arthur Weingarten, 1971 November 18 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - DEAL WITH THE DEVIL by Robert C. Dennis, 1971 October 25 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - THE SENTINELS by Alvin Boretz, 1971 May 21 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - THE MEDICINE MEN, 1971 May 20 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - THE TWENTY PESO MICHELANGELO by Meyer Dolinsky, 1972 (Box 43a, Folder 1)
    - THE STEEL ZOO by Richard Landau, 1972 (Box 43a, Folder 2)
      Includes memo from Rick Husky to Tony Barrett.
    - STEAL TO ORDER outline by Arthur Weingarten, undated (Box 43a, Folder 3)
    - AN OLD CHINESE PROVERB by Irv Pearlberg, 1970 (Box 43a, Folder 4)
    - OUT OF THE MONEY by Robert C. Dennis, undated (Box 43a, Folder 5)
    - A PLACE OF DESTRUCTION by Robert Malcolm Young, 1970 (Box 43a, Folder 6)
    - THE SUNDAY DRIVERS by Edward J. Lasko, 1968 October 21 (Box 43a, Folder 7)
    - THE TURN TO PURPLE by William Wood, 1969 January 30 (Box 43a, Folder 8)
    - MURDER, IN THE FUTURE TENSE story by James Menzies, undated (Box 43a, Folder 9)
    - Story outlines, 1969-1972 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      Includes outlines by Margaret Armen, Stephen Kandel, William Wood, Bob Heverley, Merwin Gerard, S.S. Schweitzer, Jameson Brewer, and Harriet Rochlin.
    - Story outlines, 1968-1969 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      Includes outlines by Edward J. Lasko, Robert Malcolm Young, Gwen Bagni and Paul Dubov, Alvin Sapinsley, Alvin Boretz, and Anthony Lawrence.
    - THE DECISION by Robert Malcolm Young, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - AN OLD CHINESE PROVERB by Irv Pearlberg, 1970 June 12 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      Includes notes from Aaron Spelling.
    - SPLASH ZONE by Ben Masselink, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - THE TREASURE OF THE BACK ROOM by Theodore Apstein, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - THE TROUBLE WITH JENNIE outline by Guerdon Trueblood, undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - YOU GOTTA BE A FOOTBALL HERO outline, undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - SPLASH ZONE by Ben Masselink, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      Includes standards and practices report. Also includes SHELLGAME by Edward J. Lasko, 1968 November 25.
  - The Monk (ABC, 1969)
    - Screenplay by Blake Edwards, undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Treatments, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      Includes treatments by: Richard Landau, Tony Barrett and Aaron Spelling, Brad Radnitz, and Gustave Field.
    - Thematic synopsis by Edward J. Lasko, undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Script pages by Blake Edwards and Tony Barrett, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      Includes credits.
    - Screenplay by Tony Barrett from a story by Blake Edwards, undated (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Screenplay by Tony Barrett from a story by Blake Edwards, 1969 March 23 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Screenplay by Tony Barrett from a story by Blake Edwards, 1969 March 24 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Screenplay by Tony Barrett from a story by Blake Edwards, 1969 May 1 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Script pages and notes by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 56a, Folder 1)
      Also includes a call sheet from Breakfast at Tiffany's (Paramount, 1961).
    - Screenplay by Tony Barrett from a story by Blake Edwards, undated (Box 56a, Folders 2-5)
  - Mr. Lucky (CBS, 1959-1960)
    - THE HARD WAY, undated (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - HIJACKED script pages by Tony Barrett, 1959 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      Includes WGA notice.
    - THE TWO MILLION DOLLAR WIDOW notice of tentative writing credits, 1959 December 22 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - VOTE THE BULLET notice of tentative writing credits, 1960 March 21 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - My Friend Irma (CBS, 1952-1954)
    - THE FISHING TRIP, 1953 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - The New Adventures of Charlie Chan (syndicated, 1957-1958)
    - THE SECRET OF THE SEA by Tony Barrett, 1956 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - CIRCLE OF FEAR notes, outlines, and script pages by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - New York Confidential (syndicated, 1958-1959)
    - Script, undated (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Not for Hire (syndicated, 1959-1960)
    - THE BIG MAN by Tony Barrett from a story by George Slavin, 1959 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - PS1 notice of tentative writing credits, 1959 May 25 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - TEN ROUND KILL by Tony Barrett (Box 119, Folder 7)
      Includes cast list.
  - O'Conner's Ocean (NBC, 1960)
    This was intended as a series but never got picked up. The pilot was broadcast as a movie on 1960 December 13.
    - A MEDAL FOR JOEY by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - CLOSE-UP ON MURDER [empty folder], undated (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Contract and notes, 1960 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - TOY TIGER, undated (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - DEADLY IS AS DEADLY DOES by Al C. Ward, undated (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and notes, 1960 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - DEATH IS A WRITTEN WORD, 1960 March 15 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - DEADLY IS AS DEADLY DOES [empty folder], undated (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - DEATH IS A WRITTEN WORD, 1960 March 9 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - The Pepsi-Cola Playhouse (ABC, 1953-1955)
    - DEATH HAS A SYSTEM by Fenton W. Earnshaw from a story by Ric Vollaerts, 1955 August 17 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Peter Gunn (NBC, 1958-1960; ABC, 1960-1961)
    - THE MURDER CLAUSE notice of tentative writing credits, 1960 February 8 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - THE PASSENGER script pages by Tony Barrett, 1960 July 13 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - A PENNY SAVED notes and script pages by Tony Barrett, 1960 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - PORTRAIT IN LEATHER notes and script pages by Tony Barrett, 1960 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - THE PRICE IS MURDER script pages by Tony Barrett, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - PROTECTION notes and script pages by Tony Barrett, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - THE RIFLE script pages by Tony Barrett, 1959 August 31 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - ROUGH BUCK notes and script pages by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - SEE NO EVIL script pages by Tony Barrett, 1959 September 29 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - SEPI script pages by Tony Barrett, 1960 September 21 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - SHORT A MOTIVE notes and script pages by Tony Barrett, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - SING A SONG OF MURDER script pages by Tony Barrett, 1959 December 23 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - SKIN DEEP notes and script pages by Tony and Steffi Barrett, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - A SLIGHT TOUCH OF HOMICIDE notice of tentative writing credits, 1960 February 19 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - SPELL OF MURDER notice of tentative writing credits, 1959 November 12 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - TAKE FIVE FOR MURDER by Tony Barrett, 1960 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - A TENDER TOUCH script pages by Tony Barrett, 1960 July 19 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - TERROR ON THE CAMPUS script pages by Tony Barrett, 1959 June 27 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - TILL DEATH DO US PART by Tony Barrett, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - WINGS OF AN ANGEL script pages by Tony Barrett, 1960 February 26 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - WITNESS IN THE WINDOW notice of tentative writing credits, 1960 March 14 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - THE WOLFE CASE script pages by Tony Barrett, 1959 September 23 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - THE ROYAL ROUST by Tony Barrett and Lewis Reed, 1960 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - THE YOUNG ASSASSINS by Tony Barrett and Lewis Reed, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - SEND A THIEF by Tony Barrett and Lewis Reed, 1959 November 14 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - DEATH IS A FOUR-LETTER WORD by Steffi and Tony Barrett, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      Includes: notes, contract, production documents, trade papers for 1961 March 13.
    - DEATH IS A RED ROSE notice of tentative writing credits, 1959 August 10 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - DEATH IS A SORE LOSER by Tony Barrett, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - THE DEATH WATCH script pages by Tony Barrett, 1960 February 18 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - THE DIRTY WORD notes, undated (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - DREAM BIG, DREAM DEADLY notes, undated (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - THE DUMMY script pages by Tony Barrett, 1960 January 27 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - EDGE OF THE KNIFE by Tony and Steffi Barrett, 1959 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - THE FEATHERED DOLL notice of tentative writing credits, 1959 August 28 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - THE GRUDGE notice of tentative writing credits, 1959 November 20 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - THE FUSE, undated (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - FILL THE CUP script pages by Tony Barrett, 1959 July 10 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - THE HEIRESS script pages by Tony Barrett, 1960 April 18 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - THE JUDGEMENT notice of tentative writing credits, 1960 August 18 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - KIDNAP script pages by Tony Barrett, 1959 August 21 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - LETTER OF THE LAW script pages by Tony Barrett, 1960 April 5 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - THE LONG, LONG RIDE notice of tentative writing credits, 1960 January 27 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - MASK OF MURDER script pages by Tony Barrett, 1960 July 18 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - THE MURDER BOND script pages by Tony Barrett, 1960 December 28 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - A MATTER OF POLICY by Steffi and Tony Barrett, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - THE LONG GREEN KILL by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - LAST RESORT notes and script pages by Steffi Barrett, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 22)
      Includes contract.
    - KILL FROM NOWHERE by Tony and Steffi Barrett, 1959 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - A KILL AND A HALF by Tony Barrett, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - BABY SHOES by Lewis Reed and Tony Barrett, 1960 April 20 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - DOWN THE DRAIN by Blake Edwards, 1960 April 5 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - THE GRUDGE by Lewis Reed and Tony Barrett, undated (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - BULLET FOR A BADGE by Tony and Steffi Barrett, 1959 March 18 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - BULLET IN ESCROW by Lewis Reed and Tony Barrett, 1960 October 11 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - A BULLET FOR THE BOY by Steffi and Tony Barrett, 1961 February 20 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - THE DIRTY WORD by Tony Barrett, 1958 December 10 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - DEATH IS A FOUR-LETTER WORD by Steffi and Tony Barrett, 1961 March 1 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - CRY LOVE...CRY MURDER by Tony Barrett, 1960 December 14 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Budgets, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - WOMAN FROM NOWHERE notes and outlines, undated (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - BABY SHOES script pages by Tony Barrett, 1960 May 2 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - THE BEST LAID PLANS script pages by Tony Barrett, 1960 March 7 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - BULLET FOR A BADGE by Tony and Steffi Barrett, 1959 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - A BULLET FOR THE BOY by Steffi and Tony Barrett, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - BULLET IN ESCROW script pages by Tony Barrett, 1960 October 11 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - THE CANDIDATE notice of tentative writing credits., 1960 August 23 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - COME DANCE WITH ME -- AND DIE by Tony Barrett, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - THE COMIC notice of tentative writing credits, 1959 July 16 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - THE CROSSBOW notice of tentative writing credits, 1960 April 19 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - CRY LOVE...CRY MURDER notes, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - THE DEADLY PROPOSITION script pages by Tony Barrett, 1960 January 18 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - DEATH ACROSS THE BOARD by Tony Barrett, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - THE DEATH FRAME notice of tentative writing credits, 1960 August 30 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - THE TORCH notes and script pages, 1960-1961 (Box 67, Folder 16)
      Also includes schedule of episodes and a clipping.
    - DEADLY INTRUSION notes and script pages by Steffi Barrett, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Set designs, undated (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - ...THAN A SERPENT'S TOOTH by Tony Barrett, 1960 October 24 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - TERROR ON THE CAMPUS by Tony Barrett and Lewis Reed, 1959 June 27 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - 'TIL DEATH US DO PART by Tony Barrett, 1961 January 26 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - SKIN DEEP by Tony and Steffi Barrett, undated (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - THE MURDER BOND by Tony Barrett and Lewis Reed, 1960 December 28 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - SEPI by Tony Barrett from a story by Lester Aaron Pine, 1960 September 21 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - ROUGH BUCK by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Philip Marlowe (ABC, 1959-1960)
    - Outlines and script pages, undated (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - THEME SONG, undated (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Playhouse 90 (CBS, 1956-1961)
    - THE STARLET by Aaron Spelling, 1958 April 18 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Public Defender (CBS, 1954-1955)
    - THE VANDALS by Tony Barrett, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - TALL MAN outlines by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - THE PROBLEM outlines by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Research, 1946-1947 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      Contains documents regarding a man on trial for murdering his wife.
    - STEPFATHER by Marvin Wald and Jack Jacobs, undated (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - THE SAPPHIRE MINK by Marianne Mosner and Dorothy N. Raison, undated (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - A PAIR OF GLOVES by Jerry D. Lewis, undated (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - YOUR WITNESS by William P. Rousseau, 1954 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      Includes call sheet.
  - The Richard Boone Show (NBC, 1963-1964)
    - WHERE DO YOU HIDE AN EGG? script pages and notes, 1963 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - The Rogues (NBC, 1964-1965)
    - TOYTIME by Walter Black, 1962-1965 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Notes and script pages, undated (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - The Rough Riders (ABC, 1958-1959)
    - THE HOLDOUT by Tony Barrett and Brad Allen, 1958-1959 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - THE DESERTERS by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - BLOOD CROP notes and outlines, undated (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Outline, undated (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Schlitz Playhouse of Stars (CBS, 1951-1959)
    - STEP RIGHT UP AND DIE outline by Anthony Barrett, 1956 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - THE BITTER LAND by Al C. Ward, 1955 December 17 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - THE FINGER OF GOD by William Bruckner from a story by Stuart Cloete, 1956 February 14 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - FORMOSA PATROL by Steve Fisher from a story by Jacland Marmur, 1956 January 18 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - GAMBLERS' LUCK by Douglas Morrow from a story by Albert Richard Wetjen, undated (Box 94, Folder 14)
      This episode may have actually aired on Studio 57 (DuMont, 1954-1958).
    - STEP RIGHT UP AND DIE as a short story by Anthony Barrett, undated (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Science Fiction Theatre (Syndicated, 1955-1957)
    - HOUR OF NIGHTMARE by Lou Huston, 1955 April 20 (Box 94, Folder 1)
      Barrett acted in this episode.
  - The Silent Service (NBC, 1957-1958)
    - THE NAUTILUS STORY by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - BOOMERANG by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - GALT script pages, undated (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - CREVALLE outlines and notes by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 101, Folder 4)
      Includes outlines for several differently titled stores.
    - THE GATO STORY by Tony Barrett, 1958 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - THE TAUTOG STORY by Tony Barrett, 1958 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - BOOMERANG by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - PETO PLUCKS SOME CHICKENS by Leonard Lee, undated (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - THE HAWKBILL'S REVENGE by Tony Barrett, 1957-1958 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - FIVE-RING CIRCUS by Robert C. Dennis, undated (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - SEANETTLE VS. U-BOAT by Sid Morse and Tony Barrett, undated (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - THE PARGO'S LUCKY SEVENTH by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - THE GUARDFISH STORY by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - THE BOWFIN STORY by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Skin Deep (unrealized)
    - Outline by Stephanie Nordli and Tony Barrett, undated (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - SKIN DEEP by Steffi and Tony Barrett, undated (Box 93, Folder 6a)
  - The Snoop Sisters (NBC, 1972-1974)
    - CORPSE AND ROBBERS by Leonard B. Stern from a story by Don Ingalls, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - BLACK DAY FOR BLUEBEARD by Jackson Gillis, Tony Barrett, Robert Foster, and Leonard Stern, 1973 (Box 46, Folders 2-3)
    - THE DEVIL MADE ME DO IT! by Tony Barrett and Robert Foster, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folders 4-5)
    - ABC formats, 1971-1973 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      Includes guidelines for The Wednesday Mystery Movie and The Mod Squad.
    - Story ideas by Ed Lasko, undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - FEAR IS A FREE THROW by Tony Barrett, Leonard Stern, Robert Foster, and Art Dales, 1973 (Box 47, Folders 1-4)
      Includes production documents. Also includes script for BLACK DAY FOR BLUEBEARD by Jackson Gillis, Tony Barrett, Robert Foster, and Leonard Stern.
    - THE GREAT TOY CAPER by Don Ingalls, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      Includes notes. Also includes story outlines by Gwen Bagni and Paul Dubov, George Baxt, Mort Fine, and Robert Hamner.
    - CORPSE AND ROBBERS production documents, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - BLACK DAY FOR BLUEBEARD production documents, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - THE DEVIL MADE ME DO IT! production documents, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Ratings, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Budgets, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - WHICH WINE GOES WITH MURDER? by Mort Fine, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - THE DEVIL MADE ME DO IT! by Tony Barrett and Robert Foster, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - BLACK DAY FOR BLUEBEARD by Jackson Gillis, Tony Barrett, and Robert Foster, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Story outlines, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      Includes outlines by Lary Alexander, Howard Browne, Don Ingalls, Leonard Stern, Dave Harmon, Max Hodge, and Ruth Flippen.
    - BLACK DAY FOR BLUEBEARD by Jackson Gillis, Tony Barrett, and Robert Foster, 1973 November 20 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      Also includes various story outlines.
    - Publicity, 1971-1973 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      Also includes publicity material for The Mod Squad.
    - FEAR IS A FREE THROW by Tony Barrett, Leonard Stern, Robert Foster, and Art Dales, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - THE DEVIL MADE ME DO IT! by Tony Barrett and Robert Foster, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - BLACK DAY FOR BLUEBEARD by Jackson Gillis, Tony Barrett, Robert Foster, and Leonard Stern, 1973 November 12 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - BAD DAY FOR BLUEBEARD by Jackson Gillis, Tony Barrett, and Robert Foster, 1973 November 21 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Story ideas by Tony Barrett, 1970-1973 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      Also includes ideas for The Mod Squad and Faraday and Company.
    - Story ideas, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - CORPSE AND ROBBERS by Leonard B. Stern from a story by Don Ingalls, 1973 November 15 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - CORPSE AND ROBBERS by Leonard B. Stern from a story by Don Ingalls, 1973 November 14 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      Includes production documents
    - FEAR IS A FREE THROW by Tony Barrett, Leonard Stern, Robert Foster, and Art Dales, 1973 (Box 50, Folders 1-3)
      Includes staff and crew list.
    - THE DEVIL MADE ME DO IT! by Tony Barrett and Robert Foster, 1973 December 19 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - FEAR IS A FREE THROW by Tony Barrett, Leonard Stern, Robert Foster, and Art Dales, 1973 (Box 51, Folders 1-3)
    - Casting, 1969-1973 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      Also includes cast list for The Monk and credits for Faraday and Company.
    - Schedules of directors' assignments, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - BLACK DAY FOR BLUEBEARD call sheets, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - THE DEVIL MADE ME DO IT! production report, 1974 January 18 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Script status reports, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Supernatural research, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Stage 7 (CBS, 1955-1956)
    - END OF THE LINE by Frederic Brady from a story by Richard H. Bell, undated (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - FLOWERS FOR CHARLEY MCDANIELS by W. Douglas Lansford and James Bloodworth from a story by F.A. Stone, 1956 July 10 (Box 93, Folder 3)
      According to the IMDB, this episode aired on Chevron Hall of Stars (Syndicated, 1956).
  - State Trooper (Syndicated, 1956-1959)
    - Story Ideas, undated (Box 82, Folder 19)
    - FULL CIRCLE by Tony Barrett, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - FULL CIRCLE by Tony Barrett, 1957 August 30 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - ROOM SERVICE FOR 321 by Lawrence Kimble, 1956 September 6 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - THE LIVE SHELL GAME by Fenton Earnshaw, 1957 June 14 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Steve Canyon (NBC, 1958-1959)
    - THE SERGEANT by Tony Barrett, 1959 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Straightaway (ABC, 1961-1962)
    - ESCAPE FROM DARKNESS by Robert Schaefer, Eric Freiwald, and John Draft from a story by Alfred Brenner, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      Includes notes. John Draft is a pseudonym for Tony Barrett.
    - A TOAST TO YESTERDAY by William Spier, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - THE ROSS REPORT by Rik Vollaerts, 1960 October 20 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - NEW GIRL IN TOWN by Harry Essex, 1961 February 22 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - JIG-SAW by Tony Barrett, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      Includes notes. Also includes script THE FINE PRINT SPELLS DEATH for The Investigators (CBS, 1961) by Tony Barrett.
    - A MOMENT IN THE SUN by Jo Pagano, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      Includes notes and Standards and Practices report.
    - THE BRIBE by David Chandler, Robert Schaefer, and Eric Freiwald, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      Includes Standards and Practices report. A WGA credit arbitration letter attributes the script to David Chandler and John Draft (Tony Barrett) from a story by David Chandler.
    - THE LEATHER DOLLAR by Tony Barrett, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - FULL CIRCLE by Tony Barrett (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - DIE LAUGHING by Tony Barrett, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - THE LEDGE by Tony Barrett, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - CROSSROAD by Bernard C. Schoenfeld and John Draft, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - HEAT-WAVE by Lewis Reed, 1961 August 7 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - THE TIN CAESAR by Elliot West, 1961 August 8 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - PLEDGE A NIGHTMARE by Lewis Reed, 1961 August 31 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      Includes Standards and Practices report.
    - CHICKEN RUN by Whitman Chambers, 1961 August 3 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - YOU'RE ONLY YOUNG TWICE by Jameson Brewer, 1961 August 24 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - PLEDGE A NIGHTMARE by Lewis Reed and John Draft from a story by Lewis Reed, 1961 September 29 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - A MOMENT IN THE SUN by Jo Pagano and John Draft from a story by Jo Pagano, 1961 September 28 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - THE BRIBE by Robert Schaefer, Eric Freiwald, and John Draft from a story by David Chandler, 1961 October 10 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - A TOAST TO YESTERDAY by William Spier and John Draft from a story by William Spier, 1961 September 26 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - The Survivors (ABC, 1969-1970)
    - THE SURVIVORS by Tony Barrett, 1967 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - CHAPTER ONE by John Wilder and Michael Gleason, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - THE SURVIVORS, 1968 January 3 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - THE SURVIVORS script pages, 1967 December 22 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - THE SURVIVORS by Harold Robbins, 1967 September 19 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Tightrope (CBS, 1959-1960)
    - GETAWAY DAY, 1959 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Outlines, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - THE LEDGE by Tony Barrett, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - COLD KILL by Tony Barrett, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - THE FRAME by Tony Barrett, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - THE KILLER by Tony Barrett, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Treasury Men in Action (ABC, 1950-1951; NBC, 1951-1955)
    - THE CASE OF THE SHOT IN THE DARK by Tony Barrett, 1955 March 29 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - THE CASE OF THE READY GUNS by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - THE CASE OF THE MAN NEXT DOOR by Tony Barrett, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 3)